Guide to the Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers AIA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V. Commercial Recordings, 1916-1992, undated; 28.5 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 19 packing boxes
  - 45 rpm Recordings, 1916-1992; 1958-1988; 7.85 Linear Feet in 13 small LP boxes
    - McCormack, John, "Songs of Ireland", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: Celtic Flavour, "A Long Way from Clare to Here" Side B: The Celtic Flavour, "Let Mr. McGuire Sit Down", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: Ryan, Pat and Cupla, "Ringsend Rose" Side B: Ryan, Pat and Cupla, "Rose of Kilkenny", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Jennings, Tom, "Songs for St. Patrick's Day", 1992 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - McCormack, John, "Sings Irish Songs, Vol 3", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: Dolan, Joe and the Drifters Showband, "The Answer to Everything" Side B: Dolan, Joe and the Drifters Showband, "When You Say I Love You", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: Mack, Eddie and the Columbia, "Someday You'll Call My Name" Side B: Mack, Eddie and the Columbia, "Devoted to You", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: The Freshmen, "Papa-Oom-Mow-Mow" Side B: The Freshmen, "Lets Dance", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: The Bye-Laws, "Then You Can Tell Me Goodbye" Side B: The Bye-Laws, "Come On Over to My Place", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: The Cadets, "Hello Trouble" Side B: The Cadets, "Our First Quarrel", 1963 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Cahill, Joe, "Songs of the Emerald Isle", 1962 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot and the Plainsmen, "Twenty One Years" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot and the Plainsmen, "Sing Me Back Home", 1970 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot, "Sailing Home" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot, "Road to Malinmore", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: Price, David, "The World Lost a Man" Side B: Price, David, "I Need a Friend", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: Malone, Tony, "A Beggin' I Will Go" Side B: Malone, Tony, "John Paul O'Reilly", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: Hughes, Anthony & the Ventures, "A Little Wind Up Doll" Side B: Hughes, Anthony & the Ventures, "When You Meet Marianne", 1967 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: The Airchords, "Piccolo Man" Side B: The Airchords, "Walking On New Grass", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Side A: Tina & the Mexicans, "One Love Two" Side B: Tina & the Mexicans, "Longing to Hold You", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Martin, Glen and the New Blues, "Don't Say A Word", 1972 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Side A: McEvoy, Johnny, "My Mary of the Curling Hair" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "Hickory Wind", 1969 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: Reilly, Paddy, "The Town I Loved So Well" Side B: Reilly, Paddy, "What Colour is God's Skin", 1974 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Dear Old Athlone" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "Willow, Green Willow", 1976 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: Lyons, Pat and the Hi-Spots Showband, "The Shannon" Side B: Wrenn, Mossie, and the Hi-Spots Showband, "Goodbye Mick", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: McEvoy, Johnny, "Rose of Allendale" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "Life of the Rover", 1975 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: Henry, Dermot and the Virginians, "If Those Lips Could Only Speak" Side B: Henry, Dermot and the Virginians, "Jody and the Kid" and "The Deepening Snow", 1970 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Side A: Day, Paddy, "Shanagolden" Side B: Day, Paddy, "Far Away in Australia", 1970 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry and the Mighty Avons, "The Fugitive" Side B: Cunningham, Larry and the Mighty Avons, "The Emigrant", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - The Galloglass Ceili Band, "Dancing 'Round Ireland, Part 2", 1966 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Side A: Roche, Jackie and His Irish Dance Band, "Versouviana" Side B: Roche, Jackie and His Irish Dance Band, "Irish Polka", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 65)
    - Side A: The Johnstons, "Going Home" Side B: The Johnstons, "The Travelling People", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 66)
    - Side A: The Travellers, "Erin's Flag" Side B: The Travellers, "Belfast Brigade", 1968 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 67)
    - Side A: Casterbridge Union, "Highland Paddy" Side B: Casterbridge Union, "Bold Tenant Farmer", undated (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 68)
    - Side A: Gill, Earl, "Sunset" Side B: Gill, Earl, "If I Could Choose", 1967 (Box 79, Sound disc--vinyl 69)
    - Side A: Grace, Brendan, "Cushy Butterfield" Side B: Grace, Brendan, "Down By The Glenside", 1972 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Bishop & Seeger, "Run Children Run" Side B: Bishop & Seeger, "My Brother John", 1987 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Lynch, Pat & The Airchords, "Kinsale" Side B: Lynch, Pat & The Airchords, "Harbour Of Love", 1968 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: The Wolfhound, "Provie Lullaby" Side B: The Wolfhound, "My Mary Of The Curling Hair", 1973 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: McCann, Jim, "Meet Me At The Pillar" Side B: McCann, Jim, "The Sally Gardens", 1987 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: Murphy, John, "The Lark" Side B: Murphy, John, "Galway Girl", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: Doyle, Danny, "Finnegan Are You Really Dead?" Side B: Doyle, Danny, "The Simple Telling Of Finnegan's Wake", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "My Heart Is In Ireland" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "Michael Collins", 1985 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: The Wolfe Tones, "Dreams Of Home" Side B: The Wolfe Tones, "Far Away In Australia", 1986 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: Reilly, Paddy, "My Lovely Rose Of Clare" Side B: Reilly, Paddy, "Sweet Rathcoole", 1984 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Kelly, Dermot, "The Cliffs Of Moher" Side B: Kelly, Dermot, "The Publican Joseph McHugh", 1980 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: McCarthy, Seán, "Your Land" Side B: McCarthy, Seán, "New Land", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Coll, Brian, "Moon Behind The Hill" Side B: Coll, Brian, "Candy Kisses", 1978 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Fahey, Mary, "Father Mullan" Side B: Fahey, Mary, "The Wearing Of The Green", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Bridie, "Johnny Me Love" and "Rose Of Kilkenny" Side B: Gallagher, Bridie, "Johnny Me Love" and "Rose Of Kilkenny", 1960 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean and The Hoedowners, "Old Fenian Gun" Side B: Dunphy, Sean and The Hoedowners, "I'm Gonna Be A Country Boy Again", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "The Rakes Of Mallow" and "Dohn Express" Side B: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Callum Beg" and "My Little Jimmy", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean and The Hoedowners, "The Johnny Thompson Song" and "Flower of Macroom" Side B: Dunphy, Sean and The Hoedowners, "Danny Boy" and "Black & Tan Gun", 1966 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean and The Hoedowners, "4033" Side B: Dunphy, Sean and The Hoedowners, "Come To The Bower", 1967 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: O"Donnell, Eugene and Jerry Wallace, "Kilkenny Races" and "Madame Bonaparte" Side B: O'Donnell, Eugene and Jerry Wallace, "The Hurling Boys" and "Three Sea Captains", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: Begley, Philomena and The Old Cross Bandshow, "Old Ardbo" Side B: Begley, Philomena and The Old Cross Bandshow, "The Wild Side Of Life", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: The Chieftains, "The Morning Dew" Side B: The Chieftans, "The Tip of the Whistle", 1973 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: Hogan, Brendan & The Moonshiners, "The Old Bog Road" Side B: Hogan, Brendan & The Moonshiners, "Bold Robert Emmet", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Cameron, Jim and His Band, "La Russe" Side B: Cameron, Jim and His Band, "Comin' Through The Rye", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Four Green Fields" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "When Johnny Comes Marching Home", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Connolly, Mary, "Come Back Home To Erin" Side B: Connolly, Mary, "Connemara Lullaby", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Miller, Maureen, "The Moon Behind The Hill" and "Sliabh Na Mban" Side B: Miller, Maureen, "An Chuilfhionn" and "The Castle Of Dromore", 1963 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Foley, Connie with Paddy Noonan's Orchestra, "Sean South of Garryowen" Side B: Foley, Connie with Paddy Noonan's Orchestra, "Down By The Tanyard Side", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: Rock, Dickie, Miami & Strings, "Every Step Of The Way" Side B: Rock, Dickie, Miami & Strings, "Rock And Roll Music", 1965 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Mitchell, Eddy and The Patriots, "Joseph McCann" Side B: Mitchell, Eddy and The Patriots, "This Is My Dream", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: McBride, Frankie, "Forty Shades Of Green" Side B: McBride, Frankie, "How Are Things In Glocca Morra", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: The Mexicans, "Without Your Love" Side B: The Mexicans, "Ashtrays & Candlesticks", 1968 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: The Wolfetones, "The Man From Mullingar" Side B: The Wolfetones, "Down By The Liffey Side", 1966 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: The Young Lindsay Singers, "Froinsias" Side B: Devally, Liam, Aedin Ni Choileain and The Young Lindsay Singers, "Is Mise An Tiarna", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Slaney Valley" Side B: Cunningham, Larry,"I Was Coming Home To You", 1971 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: Carroll, Padraig, "Reel: The Moving Cloud", "Waltz: Lovely Leitrim" and "Quickstep: Irish Soldier Laddie" Side B: Carroll, Padraig, "Waltz: Jaquelin Waltz" and "Quickstep: Whistling Rufus", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: Drennan, Tommy and The Monarchs, "Little Boy Lost" Side B: Drennan, Tommy and The Monarchs, "Day Is Done", 1970 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: Vampires, "Do You Wanna Dance" Side B: Vampires, "My Girl", 1968 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: The Broadsiders, "The Shores Of Amerikay" Side B: The Broadsiders, "Bottle of Wine", 1967 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: The Irish Balladeers, "The Bold Black And Tan" Side B: The Irish Balladeers, "The Orange, White and Green", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: Carroll, Padraig and Mary McGonigle, "The Mason's Apron" and "The Harvest Home" Side B: Carroll, Padraig and Mary McGonigle, "Dan O'Hara" and "The Alpine Slopes", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: The Moonlighters, "The Derry Civil Rights Song" Side B: The Moonlighters, "The Sally Gardens", The Bag O'Spuds" and "The Copperplate", 1968 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: Margo & The Keynotes, "Bonny Irish Boy" Side B: Margo & The Keynotes, "Dear God", 1968 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: Finley, Brian and Mighty Avons, "Ireland's 32" Side B: Smith, Jimmy and Mighty Avons, "Jody And The Kid", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: The Traditional Irish Musicians Association, "George White's Favorite", Miss Monaghan's" and "The Copperplate" Side B: The Traditional Irish Musicians Association, "Mary Ann", "The Dark Girl" and "Antrim Hills", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: The Wolfe Tones, "Banks Of The Ohio" Side B: The Wolfe Tones, "The Gay Galty Mountains", 1968 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: The Spinners, "The Orange And The Green" Side B: The Spinners, "Mrs. Houlighan's Christmas Cake", 1965 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: Flynn, Johnny Showband, "The Dying Rebel" Side B: Flynn, Johnny Showband, "A Word Or Two To Mary", 1969 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: Connolly, Mary, "A Nobleman's Wedding" Side B: Connolly, Mary, "Home to Mayo", 1968 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: O'Connor, John, Dermot Smith & The Cavanairs, "Lough Gowna's Lovely Shores" Side B: Smith, Dermot & The Cavanairs, "Ye Lakes And Vales Of Breffni", 1969 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: The Rhythm Stars, "The Rose Of Roscommon" Side B: The Rhythm Stars, "Lough Gownas' Lovely Shores", 1969 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: Williams, Michael, "Our Hero John Kennedy" Side B: Williams, Michael, "Moon Over Castlerea", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: Gunner, Jim, "Men Of Ireland's 32" Side B: Gunner, Jim, "The West's Awake", 1966 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Murray, Frank, "Misty Rolling Midlands" Side B: Murray, Frank, "The Irish Rebel", 1968 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Side A: The Hi-Lows, "Maureen Alanna" Side B: The Hi-Lows, "Sweethearts In Heaven", 1968 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Side A: Smyth, Pat and The Johnny Flynn Showband, "Black And Tan Gun" Side B: Smyth, Pat and The Johnny Flynn Showband, "Your Mother's Prayer", 1966 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Bridie, "The Kylermore Pass" Side B: Gallagher, Bridie, "Cutting The Corn In Cresslaugh", 1958 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry "Larry Cunningham Show" (No Side B), Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: King, Arlene and The Carlton Showband, "The Merry Ploughboy" Side B: The Carlton Showband, "Reilly's Daughter", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: The Johnstons, "The Alamo" Side B: The Johnstons, "The Life Of The Rover", 1966 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: McBride, Frankie & The Polka Dots, "The Blackboard Of My Heart" Side B: McBride, Frankie & The Polka Dots, "A Cottage In Old Donegal", 1967 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Forever And Ever" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "I'm Just A Country Girl (Boy)", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Daly, Pat and Paddy Noonan (Empty Sleeve), Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - Side A: Knowles, Sonny and Seinnteoiri Ian Henry, "Mí Iomlán" Side B: Christopher, Johnny and Seinnteoiri Ian Henry, "Siúinín", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Side A: Sherlock, Fergus, "The Croppy Boy" and "The Emerald Isle Express" Side B: O'Regan, Donal, "The felons of our land" and "She lived beside the Anner" (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 65)
    - Side A: The Millionaires, "The Merry Ploughboy" Side B: The Millionaires, "The Sea Around Us", 1966 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 66)
    - Side A: Shand, Jimmy and His Band, "Heartfell Polka" Side B: Shand, Jimmy and His Band, "The bottom of the Punch Bowl" and "Kate Dalrymple", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 67)
    - Side A: O'Hara, Shay & The Premier Aces, "Irish Soldier Boy" Side B: O'Hara, Shay & The Premier Aces, "Two Little Boys", 1969 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 68)
    - Side A: Tom, Big & The Mainliners, "I Love You Still" Side B: Tom, Big & The Mainliners, "Freight Train" and "The Pain Of Loving You", 1972 (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 69)
    - Side A: Roper, Pat & The Spotlights, "The Ring Your Mother Wore" Side B: Roper, Pat & The Spotlights, "The Northern Lights Of Old Aberdeen", Undated (Box 80, Sound disc--vinyl 70)
    - Side A: McGee, Charlie, "Thank God for John F. Kennedy" and "The Roads of Donegal" Side B: McGee, Charlie, "Ballad of Johnny Doran" and "City Named Derry", 1963 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Greehy, Anne, "The Forty Shades Of Green" Side B: Greehy, Anne, "How Are Things In Glocca Morra", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Dana, "All Kinds of Everything" Side B: Dana, "Channel Breeze", 1970 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: O'Neill, James, "Pub With No Beer" Side B: O'Neill, James, "When Peggy O'Dea Came To Mullinalee", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: Cities Service Band of America, "Trumpet Polka" Side B: Cities Service Band of America, "Gary Owen", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: Purcell, Noel, "The Dublin Saunter" Side B: Purcell, Noel, "The Man My Mother Married", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: The Hoedowners, "True Love's A Blessing" Side B: The Hoedowners, "Showball Crazy", 1966 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "Dear Little Boy Of Mine" and "Sweet Kitty Kelly" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "The Toast Of An Irish Colleen" and "Dear Old Claudy Town", 1960 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Flaherty, Connie, "My Last Wish" Side B: Carrig, Johnny, "The Ballad Of Lord Nelson", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: The Ludlows, "The Sea Around Us" Side B: The Ludlows, "The Butcher Boy", 1966 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: The McNulty Family, "When You're Winging Your Way Back To Ireland" Side B: The McNulty Family, "Someone's Waiting For Me Back In Ireland", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Flaherty, Connie, "My Last Wish" Side B: Carrig, Johnny, "The Ballad Of Lord Nelson", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: The Blarney Folk, "The Merry Ploughboy" Side B: The Blarney Folk, "The Beggarman", 1966 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: O'Donnell, Eugene, "King Of The Fairies" and "The Lodge Road" Side B: O'Donnell, Eugene, "St. Patrick's Day" and "Planxty O'Donnell", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: Johnny Flynn Showband, "You Took Her Off My Hands (Now Please Take Her Off My Mind)" Side B: Johnny Flynn Showband, "Hoots Mon Twist", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: The Tinkers, "The Rising Of The Moon" Side B: The Tinkers, "Tell Ireland I Still Miss Her", 1966 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: Doris, Malachy, "Walls of Limerick" Side B: Doris, Malachy, "Irish Hornpipe" and "Irish Barn Dance", 1961 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: Casson, Christopher, "Bold Robert Emmett" and "Adieu to Ballyshannon" Side B: Casson, Christopher, "The Road To The Isles" and "Skye Boat Song", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: The Accadians, "Wild Goose Chase" Side B: The Accadians, "Irish As Irish Can Be", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: McDaniels, Maisie, "Lovely Armoy" Side B: McDaniels, Maisie, "Forty Shades Of Green", 1961 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: Duffy, Teresa, "Lilly McNally MacNair" and "Coortin' In The Kitchen" Side B: Duffy, Teresa, "Between You And Me" and "I Don't Mind If I Do", 1958 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: Brady, Willie, "Paddy McGinty's Goat" Side B: Brady, Willie, "Finnigan's Ball", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "4033" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Come To The Bower", 1967 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Royal Blues Showband, "Little Rosa" Side B: Royal Blues Showband, "Love's Gonna Live Here", 1965 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: Doris, Malachy, "Pride of Erin" and "Sweets of May" Side B: Doris, Malachy, "Siege of Ennis", 1961 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: O'Neill, John, "Medley of Marches" and "Medley of Hornpipes" Side B: O'Neill, John, "Medley of Waltzes" and "Medley of Jigs", 1963 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "Lonely Woods Of Upton" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Yellow Haired Woman", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Among The Wicklow Hills" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "The World You Left Behind", 1966 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: O'Kelly, Betty, "Connemara Shore" Side B: O'Kelly, Betty, "The Green Glens of Antrim", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "The Man From Mullingar" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "Down By The Liffey Side", 1966 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: O'Neill, James, "The Homes Of Donegal" Side B: O'Neill, James, "The Country I'm Leaving Behind", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Owens, Jesse, "Off To Dublin In The Green" Side B: The Abbey Tavern Singers, "The Gallant Forty Twa'", 1966 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "Spanish Lady" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "Down In The Mines", 1965 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: O'Gill, Darby, "Poor Poor Farmer" Side B: O'Gill, Darby, "Hairy Eggs and Bacon", 1971 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: Hanna, Fred, "Irish Reels" and "Irish Marches" Side B: Hanna, Fred, "Hornpipes" and "Irish Jigs", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: Brady, Willie, "Tread On The Tail Of Me Coat" Side B: Brady, Willie, "Mother Malone", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "The Old Bog Road" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Galway Bay", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: McGonigle, Mary, "Farewell to the Green Hills of Erin" Side B: McGonigle, Mary, "My Hometown in Co. Mayo", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: Daly, Glen, "Sean South" and "The Dying Rebel" Side B: Daly, Glen, "Three Leaves Of Emerald Green" and "Shore of Bantry Bay", 1962 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: Lochlainn, Nic, "Spailpin a Run" and "Eamonn an Chnuic" Side B: Lochlainn, Nic, "Taim Breoite go leor" and "O bhean an ti", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: The Carlton Showband, "The Merry Ploughboy" Side B: The Carlton Showband, "Reilly's Daughter", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Don't Cry My Love" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Bye, Bye, Blackbird", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: Hanna, Fred, "Irish Marches No. 2" and "Irish Military Two Step No. 2" Side B: Hanna, Fred, "Irish Waltz Medley No. 2" and "Pride Of Erin No. 2", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "The Worst Mistake" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Wonderful World Of My Dreams", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: Kiernan, Danny, "I Belong To Glasgow" Side B: Kiernan, Danny, "Waggle of the Kilt", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: Brady, Willie, "Tread On The Tail Of Me Coat" Side B: Brady, Willie, "Mother Malone", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: Armstrong, Louis, "A Lot Of Livin' To Do" Side B: Armstrong, Louis, "Hello, Dolly!", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: Duffy, Teresa, "Mary of the Curling Hair" and "Rig-A-Doo" Side B: Duffy, Teresa, "The Humour Is On Me Now" and "Eileen McManus", 1958 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: McGarr, Pat, "Lark in the Morning" and "The Dear Little Shamrock/The Old Bog Road/Hills of Donegal" Side B: McGarr, Pat, "The Siege of Ennis/The Mist on the Bog" and "The Honeysuckle/The Kildare Fancy", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: McEvoy, Johnny, "Nora" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "Tarry Flynn", 1968 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: Gene and the Gents, "C'mon Everybody" Side B: Gene and the Gents, "Hound Dog", 1968 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: O'Kelly, Patricia, "Carlingford Bay" Side B: O'Kelly, Patricia, "Yesterday's Gone", 1966 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: McGarr, Jimmy, "On The One Road" Side B: McGarr, Jimmy, "The Boys From The County Cork", 1967 (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Don't Bother To Knock (Riley's Brew)" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Little Town In Old County Down", undated (Box 81, Sound disc--vinyl 54)